showingti.me 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of ShowingTime Inc.'s ("ShowingTime") sites, software and services, we believe you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, and how we use it. 

## Information We Collect From You and How We Use It

You may be registered or unregistered when you use our site, software, or services. As a registered visitor and/or customer, we require, at a minimum, your name, address, and e-mail address. We may also contact you when necessary, to follow up on the status of your registration, your thoughts on our site, software or services or to provide you with additional information you may need about ShowingTime's products and services. Information collected online is often defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable: 

  1. "Anonymous Information" refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. For instance, we may know that 500 individuals made appointments last Sunday through the site, software or services, but we do not necessarily know the names of each individual. 
  2. "Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII" refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, or postal address. We will use your PII to tailor our content, forward information to you or about you to others regarding appointment times, locations of real property and related appointment information. Your PII is necessary to provide the full functionality of the ShowingAssist and/or ShowingAlert services. ShowingTime will not sell or rent your PII for marketing purposes to a third party without your express consent. We will use Anonymous Information and PII for our internal analysis of the site, software and services. We also collect, analyze, create derivative works, repackage, sell and distribute to our customers and third-parties Anonymous Information about our customers' use of the site, software and services. These reports are made in every type of media, including, without limitation, print and electronic versions. Anonymous Information that will be disclosed will include, without limitation, the number of appointments made in a geographic area, the number of agents from each company that used the software, the number of cancellations, the relative ranking and use of the software by different companies and/or their agents, comparative information between different web sites, average price of homes viewed and scheduled, web site conversion ratios, web site activity relative to time of day, week, year, etc. You never have to answer any questions, and you can decline to provide us with information at any time. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with the services dependent upon the collection of this information, such as setting up an appointment time and sending your PII to an agent or brokerage company on the other side of the transaction. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user ID, that the site uses to track the pages you've visited or whether you are a registered user or previous user of the site, software or services. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. ShowingTime uses cookies to track visitor traffic patterns and for identity management. We Use Your IP Address and Web Browser We use your IP address as well as the URL of the Web page you were just on (known as the "Refer") to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and to communicate with you after you have sent us e-mails. We also collect and use the browser version you are using to access our site, software and services. Other Web-Site Links and Spamming. Our site includes links to other Web sites. Those sites may have different privacy policies. If you click on to another Web site, you may want to check the privacy policy of that site, which will usually be posted on that web site. ShowingTime is not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites. If you engage in activities such as spoofing, spamming, the posting of libelous, slanderous, defamatory, or infringing materials, or other unlawful acts, ShowingTime may be required to disclose your PII and other identifying information to our Web hosting provider, third parties or to government authorities. 

## Contact Information

You can direct all questions, comments and concerns to [support@showingtime.com](mailto:support@showingtime.com). We are always interested in hearing from our sites' visitors. If you provide e-mail feedback about the site or our services we may publish that feedback on our site using your name. If you send us e-mails, from time to time we may send updates to you about services which may be of interest to you. 

Last Updated: July 1, 2004
